There is weakness in ICICI Lombard as well.
You can see a cut of % coming in ICICI Lord this morning.
This stock is trading with a little more
weakness. Kunal ji,
ISI Lombard, look at the chart once, sir, see the
cut of % at this
time, there is definitely weakness visible.
In The Panchu stock, we
saw a big move two sessions ago and today some
reversal is visible but the
overall chart structure is still strong and
I think there is a big support which is
around 1650 1640, so it is possible that the
stock may consolidate a little more, take some time, if it
goes below 1640 then only
any first sign of weakness will be seen. For now, the
opinion is to hold. Keep the stop loss at 1640.
Okay, so stop loss has to be kept at 1640.
ISI Lombard, this is the counter for you which is
showing weakness today. There is a little weakness.